{
    "kind": "Dropdown",
    "questions": [
        {
            "title": "Choose the correct option.",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP6M1L4a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She __ her homework when her dad came home. ",
                    "options": [
                        "was doing",
                        "is doing",
                        "were doing",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What __ when you say him?",
                    "options": [
                        "is Peter doing",
                        "Peter did",
                        "was Peter doing",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was a lovely day. The sun __ .",
                    "options": [
                        "shines",
                        "was shining",
                        "shined",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ when I called you?",
                    "options": [
                        "Do you study",
                        "were you studying",
                        "are you studying",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ when the phone rang.",
                    "options": [
                        "I was having lunch",
                        "I had lunch",
                        "I have lunch",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Choose the correct form of the verb",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP6M3L12a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Mr. Denman is a policeman. He __ wear an uniform.",
                    "options": [
                        "have to",
                        "has to",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "She's short-sighted. She __ wear glasses to see the board. ",
                    "options": [
                        "need to",
                        "needs to",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is a library book. I __ return it back to the library.",
                    "options": [
                        "have to",
                        "has to",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "School starts at 8 o'clock. We __ wake up very early to get there on time.",
                    "options": [
                        "have to",
                        "has to",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Danny has a toothache. He __ go to the dentist.",
                    "options": [
                        "need to",
                        "needs to",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "They have a lot of homework. They __ finish now!",
                    "options": [
                        "need to",
                        "needs to",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}